export const question = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: "Mention what is JSON?",
    answer:
      "JSON is a simple data exchange format.  JSON means JavaScript Object Notation; it is language and platform independent",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Explain what is JSON objects?",
    answer:
      "An object can be defined as an unordered set of name/value pairs.  An object in JSON starts with {left brace} and finish or ends with {right brace}.  Every name is followed by: (colon) and the name/value pairs are parted by, (comma).",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Explain how to transform JSON text to a JavaScript object?",
    answer:
      "One of the common use of JSON is to collect JSON data from a web server as a file or HTTP request, and convert the JSON data to a JavaScript, ant then it avails the data in a web page",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Why must one use JSON over XML?",
    answer:
      "It is faster and lighter than XML as on the wire data format XML data is typeless while JSON objects are typed JSON types: Number, Array, Boolean, StringXML data are all string Data is readily available as JSON object is in your JavaScript Fetching values is as simple as reading from an object property in your JavaScript code",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Mention what is JSON-RPC and JSON Parser?",
    answer:
      "JSON RPC: It is a simple remote procedure call protocol same as XML-RPC although it uses the lightweight JSON format instead of XML JSON Parser: JSON parser is used to parse the JSON data into objects to use its value. It can be parsed by javaScript, PHP and jQuery",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Mention what is the file extension of JSON?",
    answer: "File extension of JSON is .json",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "Mention which function is used to convert a JSON text into an object?",
    answer: "To convert JSON text into an object “eval” function is used.",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Explain what is JSON objects?",
    answer:
      "An object can be defined as an unordered set of name/value pairs.  An object in JSON starts with {left brace} and finish or ends with {right brace}.  Every name is followed by: (colon) and the name/value pairs are parted by, (comma).",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Explain how to transform JSON text to a JavaScript object?",
    answer:
      "One of the common use of JSON is to collect JSON data from a web server as a file or HTTP request, and convert the JSON data to a JavaScript, ant then it avails the data in a web page",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Why must one use JSON over XML?",
    answer:
      "It is faster and lighter than XML as on the wire data format XML data is typeless while JSON objects are typed JSON types: Number, Array, Boolean, StringXML data are all string Data is readily available as JSON object is in your JavaScript Fetching values is as simple as reading from an object property in your JavaScript code",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Mention what are the data types supported by JSON?",
    answer:
      "Data types supported by JSON includes Number String Boolean Array Object Null ",
  },
];
